<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<content><string id="body">An update to No More Room in Hell has been released. The update will be applied automatically when you restart No More Room in Hell. The major changes include:

[h2]Changes[/h2]
[list]
[*]Improved overall melee hit detection, entities close up can now be hit more reliably
[*]Melee impacts no longer draw decals or spawn debris
[*]Melee swings can now hit multiple entities at once
[*]Mutator list is now sorted by title
[*]Reduced SKS w/ bayonet extra shove delay (1.5s -&gt; 0.5s)
[*]Reverted scoreboard "DEAD" label back to "DECEASED"
[*]Server-side Workshop error messages are now more descriptive

[*]Updated the localization files:
[list]

[*]With thanks to community translators: Blueberryy, Holy Crap, Klowby, marcielcps, Plazehorta
[*]Want to localize NMRiH to your own language? [url=https://github.com/nmrih/nmrih-localization-files]Visit our localization repository on GitHub.[/url]
[/list]
[/list]
[h2]Fixes[/h2]
[list]
[*]Fixed common Linux crash when earning an achievement
[*]Fixed death sound playing on disconnect kill
[*]Fixed disconnect kills affecting "We Got This!" achievement progress
[*]Fixed entity "ambient_fmod" playing all active sounds on client sign-in
[*]Fixed entity "point_message_multiplayer" not always updating position when following entities
[*]Fixed event "zombie_shoved" being fired when shoving players
[*]Fixed FMOD sound system crash when changing level (#1363)
[*]Fixed inconsistent volume factor on music and FMOD ambient sounds
[*]Fixed instructor hints displaying globally on dormant entity targets
[*]Fixed map localization not falling back to English when strings were missing for current language
[*]Fixed mutators not being applied on listen server restart (#1361)
[*]Fixed mutators not being reloaded on level change
[*]Fixed overlapping elements in options dialog
[*]Fixed rare crash when player who's using a supply crate leaves the game
[*]Fixed scoreboard text being truncated on lower resolutions
[*]Fixed server name being truncated on the scoreboard
[*]Fixed several issues with "ambient_fmod" entity
[*]Fixed SKS bayonet stab sound playing when hitting something else than a zombie or player
[*]Fixed supply crate getting stuck open when using player dies or leaves the game
[*]Fixed supply crate UI not closing during demo playback
[/list]
[h2]Changes for mappers and modders[/h2]
[list]
[*]Added entity "env_timer", a simple HUD timer with input controls similar to a stopwatch
[*]Added filter entity "filter_activator_player_infection", passes when player is infected, or optionally when activator is not a player
[*]Added filter support for entity "env_explosion"
[*]Added input "ToggleSound" to entity "ambient_fmod"
[*]Added "SetCauser" input to entities, sets who gets credit for an inflicting kill (e.g. from hurt trigger)
[*]Entity "trigger_keypad" now sets "OnTrigger" activator as player who input the code
[*]Fixed "ambient_fmod" inputs "IncreaseVolume" and "DecreaseVolume" not working
[/list]
[h1]Maps[/h1]

[h3]nmo_asylum[/h3]
[list]
[*]Added additional audio
[*]Added alternate key spawn to better balance objective paths
[*]Added alternate paths to bypass most of the chokepoints that would result in "Zombie Clogs"
[*]Added clipping to smooth out certain staircases, remove god-spots in the finale and prevent objective items from getting stuck places
[*]Added more signs
[*]Added more spooky stuff!
[*]Cheeky Foot Door now unlocks if you get special Foot Spawn. No more staring longingly at feet you can't reach
[*]Exorcised Ghost Bomb
[*]First half of the map has been streamlined based on objective path to be easier to navigate, and to have less dead ends
[*]Fixed collision on many, many objects
[*]Fixed hard to hear audio in finale
[*]Improved Performance in Courtyard
[*]Improvements to zombie spawning in finale section and reduced number of runners in courtyard by roughly 20%, but I'm afraid ya'll are still going to be at the mercy of the random spawning logic here, so you might not notice a difference if you're unlucky
[*]Readjusted meat health and finale duration to be more challenging
[*]Replaced a significant number of "Fake Real Doors" with real, fake doors to improve navigation
[*]Revamped Dormitory lighting to be less boring, general lighting improvements across the board
[*]Revamped spawning logic in finale to have significantly fewer runners
[*]Stuck spots on Keys, gravestones and front desk reception area have been fixed; ant-sized props removed, sorry ants
[*]Updated Navigation mesh to make zombies less dumb
[*]Various detailing improvements and misc. bug fixes
[*]You can now save the melon, a sincere apology to melon rescue teams for this oversight
[/list]
[h3]nmo_fema[/h3]
[list]
[*]Replaced ambient music from soundscape to "room" ambient
[*]Slightly changed "Pump it" challenge objective route
[/list]
[h3]nms_arpley[/h3]
[list]
[*]Fixed wrong ending wave
[/list]
[h3]nms_laundry[/h3]
[list]
[*]Extended extraction time
[*]Fixed zombies being stuck in a narrow alley spawn (extended playable area, even if they're stuck, players can kill them with melee)
[*]Landmine kills are now credited to a player who picked up the mine
[*]Landmines no longer damage players (except when infected)
[*]Reduced siren duration from 4 mins to 1 min
[*]Replaced "alert" hint icons for "cut the rope" objective with "use key" icon
[*]Van now honks its horn before it starts moving
[*]Van now won't instantly kill players
[/list]
</string><string id="subtitle"></string><string id="summary"></string><string id="title">Update 1.13.1 Released</string></content>