<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<content><string id="body">An update to No More Room in Hell has been released. The update will be applied automatically when you restart No More Room in Hell. The major changes include:

[h2]Additions[/h2]
[list]
[*]Added proportional HUD scaling support for high resolutions, this is more noticeable on 4K, ultrawide displays, etc.
[*]Added search box and "Find more..." button (that links to Workshop) in the mutator selection dialog
[/list]
[h2]Changes[/h2]
[list]
[*]Improved server performance on Linux
[*]In mutator selection dialog, clicking the list item now toggles the checkbox
[*]Increased max. FOV to 110
[*]Melee impact particles are now displayed across the arc
[*]Optimized zombie AI obstruction checks, improves performance on crowded maps
[*]Restored player freeze on extraction
[*]Server command "workshop_validate" now has a "-restore" option, recovers map entries from cache in case of accidental removals or data loss
[*]Supply crate no longer freezes players, checks for distance instead

[*]Updated the localization files:
[list]

[*]With thanks to community translators: Blueberryy, Klowby, marcielcps, Plazehorta
[*]Want to localize NMRiH to your own language? [url=https://github.com/nmrih/nmrih-localization-files]Visit our localization repository on GitHub.[/url]
[/list]
[/list]
[h2]Fixes[/h2]
[list]
[*]Fixed an issue with inaccurate melee headshots
[*]Fixed an issue with melee backing traces taking prominence over the initial swing arc (#1369)
[*]Fixed an issue with stamina being drained only on the first melee hit (#1386)
[*]Fixed background transparency issues on UI panel list items
[*]Fixed birds blocking player spawns (#1389)
[*]Fixed chainsaws rate limiting impact effects on characters
[*]Fixed entity "point_message_multiplayer" not updating for players who reconnect to the server (#1390)
[*]Fixed game state extraction commands working on dead players
[*]Fixed loading screen not scaling properly after resolution change
[*]Fixed mutator scripts being loaded twice on server init
[*]Fixed national guard announcement cooldown not resetting after map change
[*]Fixed national guard dialogue overlapping in survival mode
[*]Fixed players blocking usable objects with their bodies (#1327)
[*]Fixed players getting stuck after using a supply crate
[*]Fixed several HUD scaling issues across resolutions, incl. "Next Objective" separator clipping through text, tiny labels in ammo display, etc.
[*]Fixed supply crate HUD not always closing
[/list]
[h2]Changes for mappers and modders[/h2]
[list]
[*]Added beta version of level transition for developers, it's disabled by default, and server admins may toggle it with cvar "sv_level_transition" (#1278)
[*]Added command "RespawnDeadPlayers" to the game state functions (I/O, console, VScript)
[*]Added cvar "sv_killpenalty_score", sets score for kill penalty
[*]Added cvar "sv_resetscore", resets all player scores on round restart
[*]Added new category "Mutators" in the Workshop Publisher
[*]Added support for melee impact effect particles
[*]Added support for overriding viewmodel hands
[*]Added surface prop "no_friction"
[*]All MapHack debug spew is now behind cvar "sv_maphack_debug"
[*]Console commands "extractplayer" and "respawnplayer" now accept player name as input
[*]Entity "trigger_changelevel" is now functional on servers with level transition enabled
[*]MapHack: Fixed issues during pre-entity stage, which caused scripts to fail
[*]VScript: Added CenterPrint functions
[*]VScript: Added CNMRiH_GameRules bindings
[*]VScript: Added CNMRiH_Player functions SetHandModelOverride() and ClearHandModelOverride()
[*]VScript: Added CNMRiH_WeaponBase bindings and WeaponID enum
[*]VScript: Fixed event listeners writing bogus data on Linux
[/list]
[h1]Maps[/h1]

[h3]All maps[/h3]
[list]
[*]Added "debris" flag to all explosive gascans
[/list]
[h3]nmo_asylum[/h3]
[list]
[*]Corrected areaportal issue on a door located in the basement (#1376)
[*]Fixed office softlock (#1375)
[*]Fixed ritual meat not scaling health on player count
[/list]
[h3]nmo_broadway[/h3]
[list]
[*]Misc. fixes
[/list]
[h3]nmo_broadway2[/h3]
[list]
[*]Added ability to get welder if players don't have one during "navigate through sewers" objective route
[*]Added clipping to some railing
[*]Fixed multiple places where items could be lost
[/list]
[h3]nmo_brooklyn[/h3]
[list]
[*]Added glow for the extraction van
[/list]
[h3]nmo_cabin[/h3]
[list]
[*]Added rope for extraction helicopter to make it more clear where to go
[/list]
[h3]nmo_rockpit[/h3]
[list]
[*]Fixed softlock (#1394)
[/list]
[h3]nmo_suzhou[/h3]
[list]
[*]Clipped multiple areas where objective items could be lost
[*]Misc. tweaks
[/list]
[h3]nmo_toxteth / nmo_toxtethdark[/h3]
[list]
[*]Misc. fixes
[/list]
[h3]nmo_underground[/h3]
[list]
[*]Added few details to motel
[*]Fixed stuck spot near welder grate
[/list]
[h3]nms_camilla[/h3]
[list]
[*]Tweaked clips
[/list]
[h3]nms_drugstore[/h3]
[list]
[*]Adjusted shambler and runner spawning during the different stages of the map
[*]Fixed a doorway in zone A where zombies could get stuck
[*]Fixed a spawner where zombies could get stuck
[*]Fixed misc. issues/adjustments (#1250)
[*]Fixed prop_door having a wrong hinge axis (#1408)
[*]Fixed several z-fighting glitches in the mall
[/list]
[h3]nms_favela[/h3]
[list]
[*]Fixed wrong zone letter order
[/list]
[h3]nms_ransack[/h3]
[list]
[*]Extended extraction zone and extraction time
[*]Sparks on pawn shop door now start and stop properly when welding
[/list]
[h3]nms_silence[/h3]
[list]
[*]Removed ground fog particles that were accidentally included
[/list]
</string><string id="subtitle"></string><string id="summary"></string><string id="title">Update 1.13.2 Released</string></content>