<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<content><string id="body">An update to No More Room in Hell has been released. The update will be applied automatically when you restart No More Room in Hell. The major changes include:

[b]October 6th Hotfix:[/b] We've released a dedicated server update that fixes random spawners creating the same loot and occasional crashes with zombie attacks.
This update is optional, but all community admins are encouraged to apply it.

[h2]Additions[/h2]
[list]
[*]Added backward compatibility to demo files, fixes previously recorded demos not playing
[*]Added support for proportional fonts in closed captions (i.e. caption text isn't small anymore on resolutions higher than 1080p)
[/list]
[h2]Changes[/h2]
[list]
[*]Optimized zombie ability checks when near players, this improves performance on maps with a lot of attacking zombies
[*]Tweaked server networking settings to reduce latency on crowded maps

[*]Updated the localization files:
[list]

[*]With thanks to community translators: [b]Blueberryy, Klowby, MakinDay, marcielcps, Plazehorta[/b]
[*]Want to localize NMRiH to your own language? [url=https://github.com/nmrih/nmrih-localization-files]Visit our localization repository on GitHub.[/url]
[/list]
[/list]
[h2]Fixes[/h2]
[list]
[*]Fixed melee swings counting characters as obstructions, causing inconsistent hits and not registering all traces from the arc
[*]Fixed melee swings not dealing damage to entities you're directly facing (such as breakable boards)
[*]Fixed missing blood on view models (#1444)
[*]Fixed points not being awarded when killing turned zombies in survival
[*]Fixed potential server crashes caused by stale entity references in memory
[*]Fixed rare lag compensation crash
[*]Fixed server performance issues with zombies and overlord spawners
[*]Fixed shadow option reverting to "Medium"
[*]Fixed supply boxes closing immediately even when user is within reach
[*]Fixed supply boxes not checking use distance when attached to movement parents
[*]Fixed workshop add-ons not being properly removed from the add-on manager list after unsubscribing
[/list]
[h2]Changes for mappers and modders[/h2]
[list]
[*]Added auto-complete to console command "script_execute"
[*]Added "Unlisted" visibility option to Workshop Publisher (#1351)
[*]Fixed "ambient_fmod" sounds not following movement parents or source entities
[*]Fixed crash on nav generation when bone followers are present
[*]Fixed death notices not accounting for modded zombies who change classnames
[*]Fixed "nav_generate" not returning to same map after generation
[*]Following entities no longer require edicts: env_soundscape, func_zombie_spawn
[*]MapHack: Fixed $remove_all not working with server-only entities (#1447)
[*]MapHack: Fixed hang on pre-entity $edit_all
[*]VScript: Added CBaseEntity functions GetGroundEntity() and SetGroundEntity()
[*]VScript: Added CFuncZombieSpawn bindings
[*]VScript: Added CFunc_SafeZone bindings
[*]VScript: Added CNMRiH_BarricadePoint bindings
[*]VScript: Added CNMRiH_HealthStationLocation bindings
[*]VScript: Added COverlord_Zombie_Helper bindings
[*]VScript: Added nav mesh attribute constants
[*]VScript: Added NavMesh functions NavAreaBuildPath() and GetNavAreasFromBuildPath()
[*]VScript: Added team constants (TEAM_ANY, TEAM_UNASSIGNED, etc.)
[*]VScript: Fixed a crash when using NavMesh methods
[*]VScript: Fixed an issue with "logic_script" calling functions it doesn't own
[*]VScript: Fixed "filter_script" hijacking one another's PassesDamageFilter hook (#1434)
[*]VScript: Fixed potential crash when using debug overlay on dedicated server
[*]VScript: Fixed server-only entities incorrectly using the root scope for scripts
[/list]
[h2]Changes for server admins[/h2]
[list]
[*]Added cvar "sv_item_give", toggles medical item sharing
[*]Fixed "-tickrate" command line parameter not working on Linux dedicated servers
[/list]
[h1]Maps[/h1]

[h3]nmo_broadway2 / nmo_brooklyn / nmo_cleopas[/h3]
[list]
[*]Tweaked clips
[/list]
[h3]nmo_fema[/h3]
[list]
[*]Fixed wrong tree prop angle
[*]Tweaked clips and cubemaps
[/list]
[h3]nmo_shelter[/h3]
[list]
[*]Raised the ground in the sewer section to remove "crouch jump" requirement over infected water
[/list]
[h3]nmo_suzhou[/h3]
[list]
[*]Fixed floating barbered wire near tire fort
[*]Tweaked clips
[/list]
[h3]nmo_zephyr[/h3]
[list]
[*]Minor tweaks
[/list]
[h3]nms_arpley[/h3]
[list]
[*]Fixed cubemaps
[/list]
[h3]nms_camilla[/h3]
[list]
[*]Fixed a bug where instructor hint was following a player who activated the button
[/list]
[h3]nms_laundry[/h3]
[list]
[*]Alleys around zone B are now playable areas
[*]Reworked zombie spawn area near gas station to prevent zombies getting stuck in a door frame
[/list]
</string><string id="subtitle"></string><string id="summary"></string><string id="title">Update 1.13.4 Released</string></content>